Guide to the Hamilton Orgelman Papers MS 019
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Hamilton Orgelman Papers
1806-2001, (Bulk 1918-1972)
1918-1972
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Orgelman, Hamilton.
MS 019
15 Linear Feet, 12 boxes
Hamilton Orgelman was born in Danbury, Connecticut, on October 17, 1889. Orgelman was best known for his work with the Boy Scouts of America. The collection documents Orgelman's career and contains periodicals, correspondence, bulletins, booklets, scrapbook, photographs and memorabilia. Included also are materials relating to his son, George Orgelman who worked in the aviation industry.
Provenance
Donated to the Archives in 2004.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
Hamilton Orgelman was born in Danbury, Connecticut, on October 17, 1889. He married Margarethe Augusta Lepper on April 26, 1915, and had two children, George H. and Jean Orgelman Cooper.
He was a mason by trade, an avid fisherman, accomplished woodsman and camper. He became an amateur photographer while using a 16mm movie camera to film the first Boy Scout Jamboree in Washington, D. C., in 1937. In his later years, Orgelman chronicled Danbury's urban renewal project by filming the demolition of old buildings and construction of the new landscape.
In his youth, Hamilton Orgelman was also an enthusiastic ice skater, both as a hockey player and racing skater, and raced in the Eastern United States Ice Skating Championships in 1925.
However, Orgelman was best known for his work with the Boy Scouts of America. His first exposure to the Boy Scouts came at about the age of 18 as he was plastering the ceiling in the basement of the Church of Christ in Danbury. In 1915 Orgelman became assistant Scoutmaster of Troop 2 and shortly thereafter Scoutmaster. In the mid 1930s, Troop 2 became Troop 22. His service to scouting totaled 46 years during which time nearly 500 boys passed through his troop.
When Orgelman became Scoutmaster of Troop 2 in 1916, he introduced the program of "pioneering scouting" whereby members of his troop learned how to survive in the fields and woodlands. The skills for survival included woodcraft, survival training, leadership and personal development, patriotism, and civic service. Orgelman was taught these skills while living with his great uncle and grandfather in Carmel, New York. Both men had served three years with the Union army during the Civil War with extensive field experience.
Hamilton Orgelman died on April 21, 1974, at the age of 84.
Scope and Content Note
The Hamilton Orgelman collection focuses on his association with the Boy Scouts of America, Danbury Troop 2 / 22, from 1914 to 1974. The collection consists mainly of BSA publications such as Scouting magazine and other publications relevant to leadership, training, administrative and organizational manuals for adult leaders and Boy Scouts.
The collection spans from 1806 to 2001 with the bulk of the collection ranging from 1935-1972.
In addition to Boy Scout publications and memorabilia, the collection also contains a scrapbook (Box 4) which contains newspaper clippings, correspondence, and memorabilia of Orgelman's involvement with the BSA. Photographs of Troop 2/22 can be found in box 3, 9 and oversized box 2.
Orgelman's personal papers include information on Balmforth Avenue School. Mrs. Margarethe Lepper Orgelman, her sisters Mrs. Henriette Lepper Grinwold and Bertha Lepper, and her brother George Lepper were Miss Fanton's students at the Balmforth Avenue School in the 1900s. In addition to correspondence the files also contain photographs of Miss Adella Fanton's early classes (ca 1901-1903).
Photographs of Anna Hyatt Huntington house in Redding, Connecticut, chronicle the repair work done by masons on the chimneys of the house, presumably by the company Orgelman was associated with.
Margarethe Lepper Orgelman's childhood scrapbook can be found in box 8. There are several Woman's World stories penned under Johnny Gruelle entitled "Uncle Johnny Gruelle's Page for Good Boys and Girls" between 1919 and 1921. The scrapbook also contains post cards, religious cards and magazine clippings of children, pets, and flowers.
George H. Orgelman's, son of Hamilton Orgelman, was a newsboy for the Danbury Evening News from 1929 to 1936 when he graduated from Danbury High School. He occasionally wrote of his reminiscences of Danbury of long ago for the The News-Times. These articles are located in Oversized Box 1. The files also contain some information on his career at Chance Vought Airc
Series 1. Boy Scouts of America; Boxes 1-9 and Oversized Boxes 1-3; Arranged in alphabetical order.; Periodicals, correspondence, bulletins, booklets, scrapbook, and memorabilia.
Series 2. Personal; Boxes 3-5, 8 and Oversized Boxes 1-3; Arranged in alphabetical order.; Correspondence, photographs, periodicals, booklets, maps, programs, scrapbook and; memorabilia.
Series 3. George H. Orgelman; Box 3, 5 and Oversized Box 1; Arranged in alphabetical order.; Reports, booklets, correspondence, and memorabilia.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically within each series.
The files are grouped into 3 series:
Missing Title
Series 1. Boy Scouts of America
Series 2. Personal
Series 3. George H. Orgelman
Photographs.; Publications.; Fliers (printed matter); Booklets; Boy Scouts -- Connecticut; Danbury (Conn.); Correspondence.; Balmforth Avenue School.; Orgelman, Hamilton.; Chance Vought Corporation.; Huntington, Anna Hyatt.; Boy Scouts of America, Scatacook District.; Boy Scouts of America.; Lepper, Margarethe Augusta.; Orgelman, George H.
- Series 1: Boy Scouts of America
  - Air Scouting, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report (Eighth) of the BSA, April 15, 1918 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Annual Report (Tenth) of the BSA, April 8, 1920 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Art, Merit Badge Series, 1929 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: As the Twig Is Bent…Craftsmanship Among Boys of High School Age, 1933 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Connecticut Walk Book, Revised Edition with Ski Trails, 1940 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Forest Fire Warden Manual, State of Conn., 1935 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Forest Trees of Connecticut, 1929 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Forest Trees of Connecticut, 1931 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Fundamentals of the Boy Scout Movement, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Historic Tours of Soconyland, 1925 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Household Handbook, 1928 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: How to Organize a Troop of Boy Scouts, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: How to Swim the American Crawl, 1930 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Jamboree Trading Post Red Book, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Jamboree-ing in Washington, 1937 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Manual of Drill for Boy Scouts, 1916 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: The Pine Tree Patrol, 1918 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Quiz Book for Boy Scouts, 1927 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Red Cross Life Saving Methods, 1932 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Rules and Driving Practices, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: The Scouting Program in Protestant Churches, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Scoutmaster's Troop Program Note Book, 1933 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Songs & Scouting, 1930 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Swimming and Life Saving, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: 10 Squad Talks to Boys by 10 Famous Football Coaches, 1930 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Troop Meeting Programs, 1934 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: Uniform Badges and Insignia, 1933 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Booklet: The Yucca Patrol Idea, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Book: The Big Book of Scout Craft, 1929 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: The Book of Woodcraft by Ernest Thompson Seton, 1921 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: Boy Scout Handbook, 1963 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: Camp Cookery by Horace Kephart, 1919 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: Games and Recreational Methods by C. F. Smith, 1925 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: Handbook for Boys, 1942 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: Handbook for Patrol Leaders, 1929, 1931, 1944 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: Handbook for Scoutmasters, Volume 1 & 2, 1936, 1938 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: The "How" Book of Scouting, undated (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: Prize-Contest Recitations, by Geo. T. Angell, 1917 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Book: Scout Field Book, 1944 (Box 6, Folder *)
  - Boy Scout Calendars (Norman Rockwell), 1931, 1932 (2c), 1933, 1932-1933 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Boy Scout-O-Rama, Official Souvenir Book, March 27 - 28, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Boys' Life, Our Magazine Since 1912, undated (Box not specified, Folder 3)
  - Boys Life, June 1937 (cover only) (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - The Boys World, November 21, 1931 - October 15, 1932, 1931-1932 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Camp Shearwood, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Certificates, 1923-1935 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Correspondence, 1919-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Danbury, Connecticut, ca.1910-1925 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Service Training Plan Reference Materials, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - First Annual Boy Scout Round-Up, Charter Oak Council, Souvenir Program, 11/20/1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Golden Jubilee Camporee, (5x7 b/w photograph), June 6, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hikes, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Jamboree, December 7, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Leadership Manual and Instructions, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 12-14)
  - The Local Council Exchange, Equipment Number, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Local Council Exchange, Equipment Number, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Day Parade and Track Meet, Under the auspices of the Fire Department and Boy Scouts of Ridgefield, Conn., Program, May 31, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Mid-Fairfield Council Annual Meeting, 1936-1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Mid-Fairfield Council, Annual Report of the Scout Executive, 1936 (Box OS 2)
  - Mid Fairfield Council, Executives Annual Report, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mid-Fairfield Council, Annual Report, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mid-Fairfield Council 1st & 2nd Annual Camporee, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mid-Fairfield Council 1946 Camporee, June 15-16, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mid-Fairfield Council News Bulletin, 1936-1947 (Box 1, Folder 22a)
  - Miscellaneous, 1917-1974 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Miscellaneous Memorabilia, undated (Box 5, Folder *)
  - National Council BSA, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    General note
    Scoutmaster, September 1923; Specialization Course in Troop Committee, January 31, 1935; Specialization Course in Boyology, October 16, 1935; Pack Basket Construction Certificate, May 15, 1936; The Elements of Scoutmastership, Part 1, April 17, 1936; Advanced Certificate for Serving as an Officer in a Scout.
  - National Council Registration Cards, 1926-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - National Jamboree, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - National Jamboree Clearance Certificate, July 9, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - National Jamboree Tour Information, 1935 (Box OS 3, Folder *)
  - National Jamboree, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 29-31)
  - National Jamboree (small 3-ring binder w/notes), 1937 (Box 5, Folder *)
  - National Jamboree Organization Manual, June 30-July 9, 1937 (Box OS 3, Folder *)
  - National Jamboree Patch (2), 1973 (Box 5, Folder *)
  - National Jamboree Souvenir Snapshot Folder, August 3-9, 1973 (Box 5, Folder *)
  - National Jamboree, 1964 (Box 5, Folder *)
    Penfield, NY, Troop 230, pins, insignias and neckerchief
  - The National and World Jamborees in Pictures, 1937 (Box OS 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1898-1993 (Box 4, Folder *)
  - Norwalk Council, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Norwalk Hour, February 13, 1937 (Box OS 1)
  - Official Uniforms and Equipment for the 1937Jamboree (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Pamphlets: BSA Boy's Life Promotion Plans, 1925 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: BSA Minimum Requirements for Tenderfoot, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Drill Manual arranged for Boy Scouts of America, 1918 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Healthy Teeth, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Information Folder on Church-Scout Award, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Live and let Live, 1936 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Mimetic Exercises for Boys, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: The Morse Code, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Pocket Signal Disk for Instruction and Practice, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Program for Installation of a Troop, 1922 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Rope and Its Uses, 1914 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Scout Helps: Requirements for the Tenderfoot Scout, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Requirements for the Second Class Scout, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: Requirements for the First Class Scout, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: The Scoutmaster and His Troop, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: A "Share the Work Plan" for all Troop Committeemen, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: The Treatment of Athletic Injuries, undated (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets: The Troop Committee, 1945 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Trustworthy, Loyal, Helpful, Friendly....A Profile, 1942 (Box 7, Folder *)
  - Photographs, 1920-1944 (Box 9, Folder *)
  - Photographs: One 5 x 7 b/w image (framed), 1917 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Photographs: Four 10 ½ x 10 ½ scrapbook pages with b/w photographs, ca.1930 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Photographs: Two 8 x 10 b/w images (mounted), 1935 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Photographs: One 8 x 10 b/w image of Henry Dick & Son window display commemorating Troop 2 / 22's 25th Anniversary, undated (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Poster: Boy Scout Week, Feb. 8-14 (no year given), undated (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Roosevelt Memorial Pilgrimage Programs, 1935-1936, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Rye-Me-Calendar, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Scatacook District Recognition Banquet Programs, 1969-1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Scout Administrator, Equipment Number, Nov. 1935 (2c) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The Scout Administrator (Literature of the BSA), 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Scout Administrator, Equipment Number, Nov. 1937 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Scouter, Fairfield County Council, March 1972-1982 (Box 1, Folder 40-41)
  - Scouter, Mauwehu Council, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 42-44)
  - Scouting: April 15 - December 15, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Scouting: January 15 - December 26, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 46-49)
  - Scouting: January 2 - December 18, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 50-52)
  - Scouting: January 1 - December 23, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 53-54)
  - Scouting: January - December 1921 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Scouting: April - December 30, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Scouting: January 15 - December 1923 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Scouting: September - December 1925 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Scouting: January - December, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Scouting: January - August 1927 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Scouting: February 1930 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Scouting: December 1932 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Scouting: January - December 1933 (Box 1, Folder 63-65)
  - Scouting: February - December 1934 (Box 1, Folder 66-68)
  - Scouting: January- December 1935 (Box 1, Folder 69-72)
  - Scouting: January - December 1936 (Box 1, Folder 73-75)
  - Scouting: February - December 1937 (Box 1, Folder 76-78)
  - Scouting: January - December 1938 (Box 3, Folder 65-67)
  - Scouting: January - December 1939 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Scouting: January - December 1940 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
  - Scouting: January - December 1941 (Box 2, Folder 7-12)
  - Scouting: January - December 1942 (Box 2, Folder 13-18)
  - Scouting: January - December 1943 (Box 2, Folder 19-24)
  - Scouting: January - December 1944 (Box 2, Folder 25-27)
  - Scouting: January - December 1945 (Box 2, Folder 28-30)
  - Scouting: January - May 1946 (Box 2, Folder 31-32)
  - Scouting: June - December 1947 (Box 2, Folder 33-35)
  - Scouting: January - July 1948 (Box 2, Folder 36-38)
  - Scouting: October - December 1949 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Scouting: January - May 1950 (Box 2, Folder 40-41)
  - Scouting: November 1951 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Scouting: February - April 1953 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Scouting: February 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Scouting: March - April 1956 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Scouting: May - October 1958 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Scouting: April 1959 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Scouting: January - February 1960 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Scouting: December 1964 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Scouting: February 1965 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Scouting: January - December 1966 (Box 2, Folder 51-54)
  - Scouting: January - February 1967 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Scouting: March - December 1969 (Box 2, Folder 56-58)
  - Scouting: January - December 1970 (Box 2, Folder 59-61)
  - Scouting: March - December 1971 (Box 2, Folder 62-63)
  - Scouting: January - December 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Scouting Equipment Number, Nov. 1921 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Scouting Equipment Number, Oct. 1923 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Scoutmastership Notes (Columbia Univ.), 1925-1926 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, 1935-1972 (Box 4)
  - Testimonial Dinner, November 6, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 7-7a)
  - Testimonial Guest Book and Hamilton Orgelman "Oggie" (bound correspondence), November 6, 1964 (Box OS 3, Folder *)
  - Testimonial/City of Danbury Proclamation, November 5, 1964 (Box OS 3, Folder *)
  - Testimonial/Lyndon B. Johnson 7x8 b/w photograph signed (mounted on board), undated (Box OS 3, Folder *)
  - Testimonial/Scrapbook, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 7b)
  - Troop 1, 21, 22 Charters (certificates), 1923-1944 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Troop 1, 2, 22, Charter Renewals, 1926-1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Troop 2, Record of Camp, August 1920 (Box 5, Folder *)
  - Troop 2 Record (Membership and Finances), 1915-1918 (Box 5, Folder *)
  - Troop 2 Membership (small booklet), undated (Box 5, Folder *)
  - Troop 2 Misc. Notes (small ringed binder), undated (Box 5, Folder *)
  - Troop 2 / 22 History, 1992-1993 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Troop 2 / 22 History Notes, undated (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - U. S. Army Recruiting News, Special First Corps Area Edition, July 2, 1921 (highlights Camp Devens' C.M.T. Camp (Citizens' Military Training Camps), Massachusetts. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Victory Boy, September 27, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Series 2: Personal
  - The Balance and Columbian Repository January 14, 1806 - July 29, 1806 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - School and class photographs, 1901-1910 (Box 3, Folder 11-17)
  - class Photograph Balmforth Avenue School, 1907-1908 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Biographical Information, undated (Box 3, Folder 17a)
  - B.M.P.I.U. of America (Bricklayers, Masons & Plasterers International Union), 1916-1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fishing Licenses, 1918-1920 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fishing License (Angling License/Connecticut 1930) (Box 5, Folder *)
  - Fishing Notes, 1927-1933 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The Girls' Companion, January 31, 1937 - February 21, 1937 (Box OS 1)
  - John Hancock Mutual Life Ins.Co. Booklets, 1923-1932 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    The Flag of the United States
    Mount Vernon, the Home of Washington
    George Washington, First President of the United States
    The Story of the Pilgrims
    Patriotic Songs of America
    Robert E. Lee, The Beloved General
  - Huntington, Anna Hyatt (b/w photographs), ca.1955 (Box 3, Folder 23-32)
  - Map-Bridgeport, Conn., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Map-Connecticut (State Parks & Forests), 1939 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Maps-Danbury, 1916, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous, 1914-1954 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Notebook: Amounts Paid Out & BSA, 1944-1961 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - National Sportsman, July 1920 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - National Sportsman, April 1931 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Old Timers' Athletic Association of Greater Danbury, Ninth Annual Dinner Program, September 21, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Outers' Recreation, February 1924 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Programs, 1900-1973 (Box 3, Folder 42-43)
  - Scrapbook (Margarethe A. Lepper) (fragile), ca.1919-1921 (Box 8, Folder *)
  - Taylor Opera House Programs, 1911-1915 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Series 3: George H. Orgelman
  - Chance Vought Aircraft, Inc.: Annual Report, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Chance Vought Aircraft, Inc.booklets, undated (Box 3, Folder 46-49)
    A Guide to the Engineering Professions in the Aviation Industries, 1954
    A Policy for Scientific and Professional Manpower, 1953
    How to Improve Engineering-Management Communications, 1952
    How to Improve the Utilization of Engineering Manpower, 1952
    Income and Salary Survey, 1952
    Industry's Stake in ASEE…A Message to Industrial Management, n.d.
    Recruiting College Graduate: A Guide for CompanyInterviewers, 1953
    What's in a name?
  - Careers at Chance Vought Aircraft, ca.1955 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Chance Vought Aircraft, ca.1940 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Chance Vought Move, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Chance Vought Move (2c), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Danbury News-Times, 1999-2001 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Line-O-Graph, 7 ½" and 9", undated (Box 5, Folder *)
  - Miscellaneous, 1951-1968 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - A Plan for Organizational Development, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Recruitment of Engineering Manpower, 1952-1956 (Box 3, Folder 56-61)
  - Salary and Wage Administration, Policies and Procedures, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Tomorrow's Engineering, 1954-1961 (Box 3, Folder 63-64)